<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My Digital Garden</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My Digital Garden</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Joshua Nye ©</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Nurturing Talent: A Guide to Mentoring Junior Software Developers</title>
      <link>/garden/nurturing-talent/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/garden/nurturing-talent/</guid>
      <description>Mentoring junior software developers involves creating a safe learning environment, setting clear expectations, personalizing your approach, fostering problem-solving skills, encouraging self-learning, providing constructive feedback, leading by example, promoting collaboration and networking, and maintaining a mindset of continuous learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Implementing Domain-Driven Design</title>
      <link>/library/implementing-domain-driven-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/library/implementing-domain-driven-design/</guid>
      <description>An in-depth guide that provides both theoretical understanding and practical examples for effectively applying Domain-Driven Design principles in software development projects</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Domain-Driven Design: Tackling Complexity in the Heart of Software</title>
      <link>/library/domain-driven-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/library/domain-driven-design/</guid>
      <description>A foundational book that introduces and thoroughly explores the principles and practices of Domain-Driven Design as a strategic approach to manage complexity in software development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joshua Nye</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Software Engineer</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Patterns: Elements of Reusable Object-Oriented Software</title>
      <link>/library/design-patterns/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/library/design-patterns/</guid>
      <description>A foundational text in software engineering, providing a comprehensive introduction to 23 classic design patterns that serve as enduring, language-agnostic solutions for common programming problems.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
